Kheel, Theodore W. Newspaper Clipping File 6021/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Volume 7. New York City Bus and Subway Strikes., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  December 25 1965 - January 5 1966
- Volume 7. New York City Bus and Subway Strikes., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  January 6 - 11 1966
- Volume 7. New York City Bus and Subway Strike., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  January 12 - 26 1966
- Volume 7. New York City Bus and Subway Strike and Threats., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Volume 7. New York City Bus and Subway Strike and Threats., 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Volume 7. New York City Subway and Bus Strikes and Threats., 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Volume 7. New York City Subway and Bus Strike., 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Volume 7. New York Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Volume 7. New York Magazine. Rupert Murdoch Controversy., 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Volume 7. New York Post. Gail Sheehy. Profile of Dorothy Schiff., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Volume 7. New York Times. Excerpt from Kingdom and the Power. (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Volume 7. Newspaper Disputes and Strikes. 1963 Strike. (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Volume 7. Newspaper Disputes and Strikes., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  March 30 - June 27 1965
- Volume 7. Newspaper Disputes and Strikes., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  June 30 - September 18 1965
- Volume 7. Newspaper Disputes and Strikes., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  November 18 - 24 1965
- Volume 7. Newspaper Disputes and Strikes., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  September 25 - October 9 1965
- Volume 7. Newspaper Disputes and Strikes., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  October 10 - November 16 1965
- Volume 7. Newspaper Disputes and Strikes., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Volume 9. Pennsylvania State University Controversy., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Volume 9. Samuel R Pierce, Jr., 1961-1989 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Volume 9. Plumbing Industry., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Volume 9. Police Disputes and Strikes., 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Volume 9. Police Review Board., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Queens College Controversy., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Volume 9. Punta Cana Beach Resort., 1971-1989 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Volume 9. Railroad Disputes and Strikes., 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Volume 9. Railroad Disputes and Strikes., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Volume 9. Railroad Disputes and Strikes., 1980-1983 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Volume 9. Republic National Bank., 1964-1975 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Volume 9. Sanitation Workers Disputes and Strikes., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Volume 9. Sanitation Workers Disputes and Strikes., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- PL Roy Siemiller. (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Volume 9. Stirling Homex Corp., 1969-1978 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Volume 9. Taxi Driver Disputes and Strikes., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Volume 9. Teacher Disputes and Strikes., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Volume 9. Teacher Disputes and Strikes., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Volume 9. Teacher Disputes and Strikes., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Volume 9. Teacher Disputes and Strikes., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Volume 9. Teacher Disputes and Strikes. Ocean Hill., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Volume 9. Teacher Disputes and Strikes., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Volume 9. Transit Fares. Kheel Speeches., 1955-1963 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Volume 9. Transit Fares and Tolls., 1965-1968 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Volume 9. Transit Fares and Tolls., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Volume 9. Transit Fares and Tolls., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Volume 9. Transit Fares and Tolls., 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Volume 9. Transit Fares and Tolls., 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Volume 9. Transportation Workers Union., 1958-1984 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Volume 9. Transportation Bond Issue., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 70)